Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
Benjamin Spock and Mary Morgan Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Moss, Frank E. (Box 220)
  - Moss, Henry (Box 220)
  - Moss, Norman (Box 220)
  - Mother to Mother: Another View (Box 221)
  - Mother's Day Coalition for Nuclear Disarmament (Box 221)
  - Mothers for Johnson and Humphrey (Box 221)
  - Mothers Today (Box 221)
  - Mott, Stewart Rawlings (Box 221)
  - Mountain Top Films (Box 221)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick (Box 221)
  - Ms [magazine] (Box 221)
  - Mumford, Lewis (Box 221)
  - Murphy, Mike (Box 221)
  - The Museum of Modern Art, New York, NY (Box 221)
  - Musicians United for Safe Energy (Box 221)
  - Muskie, Edmund S. (Box 221)
  - Muste, A. J. (Box 221)
  - Myrdal, Gunnar (Box 221)
  - Nader, Ralph (Box 221)
  - Natchez, Gladys (Box 221)
  - Nathan, Otto (Box 221)
  - Nathanson, Laura Walther (Box 221)
  - The Nation [magazine] (Box 221)
  - National Action Group (Box 221)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (Box 221)
  - National Anti-Klan Network (Box 221)
  - National Assembly on the Future of the Family (Box 221)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), Cleveland Branch (Box 221)
  - National Association of Broadcast Engineers and Technicians (Box 221)
  - National Association for Mental Health (Box 221)
  - National Association for Retarded Children (Box 221)
  - National Association of Social Workers (Box 221)
  - National Association on Standard Medical Vocabulary (Box 221)
  - National Audubon Society (Box 221)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC), 2 folders (Box 222)
    See also Legal files: National Broadcasting Company (NBC).
  - National Campaign for Radioactive Waste Safety (Box 222)
  - National Campaign to Stop the MX (Box 222)
  - National Center on Child Abuse and Neglect (Box 222)
  - National Center to Slash Military Spending (Box 222)
  - National Chile Center (Box 222)
  - National Citizens' Commission on International Cooperation (Box 222)
  - National Citizens Commission for the Public Schools (Box 222)
  - National Citizens Crusade Against Poverty (Box 222)
  - National Civil Liberties Clearing House (Box 222)
  - National Commission on Children (Box 222)
  - National Committee Against Mental Illness (Box 222)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (Box 222)
  - National Committee for Children and Youth (Box 222)
    See also White House Conference on Children and Youth.
  - National Committee for a Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes in Vietnam (Box 222)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress (Box 222)
  - National Committee for Free Elections in Mississippi (Box 222)
  - National Committee for the Reform of Marijuana Laws, 2 folders (Box 222)
    See also National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws.
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy (SANE), 1958-1962 (Box 222)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy (SANE), 1963-1966; 5 folders (Box 223)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy (SANE), 1967; 7 folders (Box 224)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy (SANE), 1968-1982; 5 folders (Box 225)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy (SANE), 1983-1987; undated; 6 folders (Box 226)
  - National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy (SANE), publications; 3 folders (Box 226)
  - National Committee on Health Care for the Aged (Box 226)
  - National Committee on the Emereti, Inc. (Box 226)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee (HUAC) (Box 226)
  - National Committee to Re-open the Rosenberg Case (Box 226)
  - National Committee to Repeal the McCarran Act (Box 226)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1966-1968; 7 folders (Box 227)
  - National Conference for New Politics, 1968-1987; 5 folders (Box 228)
  - National Conference for New Politics, publications (Box 229)
  - National Conference for New Politics, constitution (Box 229)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc (Box 229)
  - National Conference of Health, Welfare and Pension Plans (Box 229)
  - National Conference of Parents and Teachers (Box 229)
  - National Conference on Military Spending (Box 229)
  - National Consumers League (Box 229)
  - National Coordinating Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 229)
  - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Inc. (Box 229)
  - National Council for Children's Rights (Box 228)
  - National Council of the Churches of Christ in the U.S.A. (Box 229)
  - National Council for Civic Responsibility, See Public Affairs Institute, Washington, DC.
  - National Council of Senior Citizens, Inc. (Box 229)
  - National Council to Repeal the Draft (Box 229)
  - National Education Association (NEA) (Box 229)
  - National Educational Television and Radio Center (Box 229)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee (Box 229)
    See also Emergency Civil Liberties Committee.
  - National Enquirer (Box 229)
  - National Federation of the Blind (Box 229)
  - The National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis (Box 229)
  - National Gay Task Force (Box 229)
  - National Geographic Society (Box 229)
  - The National Institute of Child Health and Human Development (Box 229)
  - National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People (Box 229)
  - National Kidney Disease Foundation, Northern Ohio Chapter (Box 229)
  - National Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace (Box 229)
  - National Library Week (Box 229)
  - National Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 4 folders (Box 230)
  - National Museum of American History, Washington, DC (Box 230)
  - National Office of the Committee to Free the Mao Tsetung Defendants (Box 230)
  - National Organization for the Reform of Marijuana Laws, 2 folders (Box 230)
    See also National Committee for the Reform of Marijuana Laws.
  - National Organization for Women (NOW)
    - Alabama NOW Times (Box 231)
    - National NOW Times (Box 231)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1980; 6 folders (Box 231)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 232)
    - Essex County New Jersey Newsletter (Box 232)
    - Louisiana NOW Times (Box 232)
    - Membership, 2 folders (Box 232)
    - Nashville Chapter Newsletter (Box 232)
    - National Board Meeting Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 232)
    - Policy manuals (Box 232)
    - The Women's Monthly, NOW New York State (Box 232)
  - National Organization of Mothers of Twins Clubs (Box 232)
  - National Parent Teacher Association (Box 232)
  - National Peace Academy Campaign (Box 232)
  - National Peace Action Coalition (Box 232)
  - National Press Books, 2 folders (Box 232)
  - National Press Books, Inc. (Box 233)
  - National Public Radio (NPR) (Box 233)
  - National Resistance Committee (Box 233)
  - National Review (Box 233)
  - National School Board Association (Box 233)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 233)
  - National Society for Autistic Children (Box 233)
  - National Society for Crippled Children and Adults (Box 233)
  - National Student Conference Against Racism, Boston, MA (Box 233)
  - National Student Speech and Hearing Association (Box 233)
  - National Task Force on Day Care Interior Design (Box 233)
  - National Taxpayers' Union (Box 233)
  - National Town Meeting (Box 233)
  - National Welfare Rights Organization (Box 233)
  - National Women's Conference (Box 233)
  - National Youth Work Alliance (Box 233)
  - Nationwide Unemployed League, See International Workers Party.
  - Native American Solidarity Committee (Box 233)
  - The Natural Childbirth Association, Toronto, Ontario (Box 233)
  - Natural Science Museum, Cleveland, OH (Box 233)
  - Near, Holly, 2 folders (Box 233)
  - Needlman, Herbert (Box 233)
  - Negotiation Now Bulletin (Box 233)
  - Negro Actors for Action Committee (Box 233)
  - Nero, Norma (Box 233)
  - Nesbitt, E. Marcellus (Box 233)
  - Nestle Corporation, See Infant Formula Action Coalition (INFACT).
  - Nettleship, Anderson (Box 233)
  - Neubauer, Peter B. (Box 234)
  - Neuhaus, Richard J. (Box 234)
  - Neuman, Jack (Box 234)
  - Neuro-Linguistic Professional Training (Box 234)
  - New Alliance for Gay Equality (New AGE) (Box 234)
  - New America (Box 234)
  - New American Library, Inc. (NAL) (Box 234)
  - New American Movement (Box 234)
  - New China (Box 234)
  - New England Camping Association (Box 234)
  - New England Medical Center Hospitals, Boston, MA (Box 234)
  - The New Media Project (Box 234)
  - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, See National Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam.
  - New Outlook (Box 234)
  - The New Party, 7 folders (Box 234)
    See also The People's Party.
  - The New Party, 5 folders (Box 553)
  - The New Party, 2 folders (Box 235)
  - The New Republic (Box 235)
  - New School for Social Research (Box 235)
  - The New Women, New York, NY (Box 235)
  - New World Review (Box 235)
  - New York College of Podiatric Medicine (Box 235)
  - New York Graphic Society, Ltd. (Box 235)
  - New York Herald Tribune Syndicate (Box 235)
  - The New York Hospital, New York, NY (Box 235)
  - New York Institute for Child Development (Box 235)
  - New York Medical College, New York, NY (Box 235)
  - New York Medical Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 235)
  - New York Public Library (Box 235)
  - The New York Review (Box 235)
  - New York Society of Clinical Psychologists (Box 235)
  - The New York Times, 2 folders (Box 235)
  - The New York Times Book Review (Box 235)
  - New York University (Box 235)
  - The New Yorker (Box 235)
  - Newborn Rights Society (Box 235)
  - Newman, Arnold (Box 235)
  - Newman, Paul (Box 235)
  - Newsweek, 2 folders (Box 236)
  - Nguyen Dang Quang (Box 236)
  - Nguyen Thi Binh (Box 236)
  - NHK Japan Broadcasting Corporation (Box 236)
  - Nicaragua Network, 1985; 3 folders (Box 236)
  - Nicaragua Network, 1986-1994; 7 folders (Box 237)
  - Nicaraguan Literacy Crusade (Box 238)
  - The Nine Network (Box 238)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 238)
  - No Business as Usual! (Box 238)
  - Nodland, Jory (Box 238)
  - Noel-Baker, Philip (Box 238)
  - Nomura Center for Lifelong Integrated education, Tokyo, Japan (Box 238)
  - Norback & Company, Inc, Princeton, NJ (Box 238)
  - North American Congress on Latin America, Inc. (NACLA) (Box 238)
  - North American Newspaper Alliance (Box 238)
  - North Andover People for Peace (Box 238)
  - North Arkansas Community College (Box 238)
  - Northeast Arkansas Childbirth Education Association (Box 238)
  - Northern Ohio Pediatric Society (Box 238)
  - Northern Sun News (Box 238)
  - Norwich Anti-Nuclear Campaign, Norfolk, England (Box 238)
  - [University of] Notre Dame (Box 238)
  - Novak, William (Box 238)
  - NOW, See National Organization for Women (NOW).
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund (Box 238)
  - Nuclear Age Peace Foundation (Box 238)
  - Nuclear Construction Moratorium (H.R. 2608) (Box 238)
  - The Nuclear Litigation Fund (Box 238)
  - Nuclear power, includes material from various organizations, including Mobilization for Survival, Clamshell Alliance, etc.; 2 folders (Box 238)
  - Nuclear power, includes material from various organizations, including Mobilization for Survival, Clamshell Alliance, etc.; 3 folders (Box 239)
  - Nuclear Times (Box 239)
  - Nuclear Weapons Facilities Taskforce (Box 239)
  - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign (Box 239)
  - Nursery Education (Box 239)
  - The Nutrition Association, Cleveland, OH (Box 239)
  - Oakland Community College, Southfield, MI (Box 239)
  - The Observer, London, England (Box 239)
  - Ochs, Phil (Box 239)
  - O'Connor Freedom Fund (Box 239)
  - October Mobalisation, Australia (Box 239)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul (Box 239)
  - The Odyssey Press, Inc. (Box 239)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, See United States Executive Office of the President, Office of Economic Opportunity.
  - Office of Science and Technology, See also United States Executive Office of the President, Office of Science and Technology.
  - Oglesby, Carl (Box 239)
  - Ohio Business and Professional Men and Women for Kennedy-Johnson (Box 239)
  - Ohio Citizens for Action Now (Box 239)
  - Ohio Commission on Children and Youth, 2 folders (Box 240)
  - Ohio Federation of the Council for Exceptional Children (Box 240)
  - Ohio Health Letter (Box 240)
  - Ohio Osteopathic Association (Box 240)
  - Ohio Peace Action Council (Box 240)
  - Ohio School Foundation Program (Box 240)
  - Ohio State Medical Association (Box 240)
  - Ohio University Department of Child Development and Family Living (Box 240)
  - Ohioans for a Reasonable Settlement in Vietnam (Box 240)
  - Ohman, Eleanor (Box 240)
  - The Older Women's League (Box 240)
  - Olds, Sally Wendkos (Box 240)
  - Olympian International (Box 240)
  - Olympic gold medal, Spock won an Olympic gold medal in 1924, while a student at Yale, as a member of the Men's Eights Rowing Crew; the actual medal is not in the collection (Box 240)
  - Omaha World Herald (Box 240)
  - Omni [magazine] (Box 240)
  - Ontario Hospital Association, Ontario, Canada (Box 240)
  - "The Open Mind" (Box 240)
  - Operation Medic (Box 240)
  - Organization of Solidarity with the People of Asia, Africa and Latin America (Box 240)
  - Ornish, Dean (Box 240)
  - Osage Association, Inc. (Box 241)
  - Osborn, Elodie Courter (Box 241)
  - Osborn, Robert Chesley (Box 241)
  - Oshtry, Norman Alexander (Box 241)
  - Ottawa (ON) Committee for Peace and Liberation (Box 241)
  - Our Children, See Woman's Home Companion.
  - Our Lady of Providence Children's Center (Box 241)
  - Ours (Box 241)
  - Out Now! (Box 241)
  - Overlook Hospital, Summit, NJ (Box 241)
  - Oxdems' Midwest Cartoon Fund (Box 241)
  - Oxfam America (Box 241)
  - Oxford University Press, Inc. (Box 241)
  - Oxholm, Maria (Box 241)
  - Oyer, Herbert J. (Box 241)
  - Ozark Institute (Box 241)
  - Ozark Life Center (Box 241)
  - Ozawa, Seiji (Box 241)
  - The Pace Association (Box 241)
  - Pacific-10 Conference (Box 241)
  - Pacifica Radio, New York, NY (Box 241)
  - Packwood, Bob (Box 241)
  - Paese Sera (Box 241)
  - Pageant (Box 241)
  - Palm Beach Roundtable (Box 241)
  - Palmetto Alliance, Columbia, SC (Box 241)
  - Palnick, Elijah E. (Box 241)
  - Pantheon Books, 2 folders (Box 242)
  - Parade [magazine], 1984-1988; 4 folders (Box 242)
  - Paradise, Jack L. (Box 243)
  - Parallel Films (Box 243)
  - Parent Education Project, Chicago, IL (Box 243)
  - Parenting [magazine], 1985-1994; 7 folders (Box 244)
  - Parenting [magazine], 1994-1998; 5 folders (Box 245)
  - The Parent's Journal (Box 245)
  - Parents and Friends for Children's Survival (Box 245)
  - Parents and Teachers Against Violence in Education (Box 245)
  - Parents for Responsibility in the Toy Industry (Box 245)
  - Parents' Magazine (Box 245)
  - ParentTime (Box 245)
  - Paris Match (Box 246)
  - The Park School of Baltimore (Box 246)
  - Parker, Steven (Box 246)
  - Parkinson, C. Northcote (Box 246)
  - Passages [magazine] (Box 246)
  - The Pat Collins Show (Box 246)
  - Pauling, Linus (Box 246)
  - Pax (Box 246)
  - Peace Abbey (Box 246)
  - Peace Action, See National Committee for a SANE Nuclear Policy, Inc.
  - Peace Action Council of Southern California (Box 246)
  - Peace and Freedom Party, 2 folders (Box 246)
  - Peace and Freedom Party, 5 folders (Box 247)
  - Peace At Home Family Shelter, Fayetteville, AR (Box 247)
  - Peace Council of the German Democratic Republic (Box 247)
  - Peace groups, miscellaneous (Box 247)
  - Peace Hostage Exchange Foundation (Box 247)
  - Peace House, Ashland, OR (Box 247)
  - Peace Independents (Box 247)
  - Peace Links Worldwide, Women Against Nuclear War (Box 248)
  - Peace Organizing Committee, Fayetteville, AR (Box 248)
  - Peace Productions (Box 248)
  - Peace songs (Box 248)
  - Peace Through Communication (Box 248)
  - Peace Through Law Education Fund (Box 248)
  - Peace Torch Marathon (Box 248)
  - Peale, Norman Vincent (Box 248)
  - Pearson, Drew (Box 248)
  - Pediatric Clinics of North America (Box 248)
  - The Pediatric Foundation, New York, NY (Box 248)
  - Pediatric News (Box 248)
  - Pediatricians & Parents for People (Box 248)
  - Pediatrics (Box 248)
  - Pell, Claiborne (Box 248)
  - Penguin Books USA (Box 248)
  - Pennsylvania Conference on Aging (Box 248)
  - Pennsylvania State University (Box 248)
  - The Pentagon Papers Fund (Box 248)
  - People [magazine] (Box 248)
  - People Against Nuclear Energy (Box 248)
  - People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) (Box 248)
  - People to People, 2 folders (Box 248)
  - People's Action for Safe Energy (Box 248)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilization (Box 248)
  - Peoples' Assembly (Box 248)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice (Box 248)
  - Peoples Committee for Metropolitan General Hospital, Cleveland, OH (Box 248)
  - People's Party
    - Fundraising, 2 folders (Box 249)
    - General, 1971-1972; 4 folders (Box 249)
    - General, 1972-1973; 5 folders (Box 250)
    - General, 1974-1980; 6 folders (Box 251)
    - National Convention 1972, 2 folders (Box 252)
    - National Convention 1974 (Box 252)
    - Presidential Campaign 1972, printed material; schedules and events; 2 folders (Box 252)
    - Publications, Grass Roots, 3 folders (Box 253)
    - Publications, regional newsletters (Box 253)
    - Publications, miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 253)
  - People's Peace Treaty (Box 254)
  - Pepper, Claude (Box 254)
  - Pepper, William F. (Box 254)
  - Percy, Charles H. (Box 254)
  - Perera, Victor (Box 254)
  - Peretz, Martin (Box 254)
  - Perkins, Faith (Box 254)
  - Perry Nuclear Power Plant, Perry, OH (Box 254)
  - Pertz, Sylvia (Box 254)
  - Peter, Laurence J. (Box 254)
  - Pfister, Fred R. (Box 254)
  - Pham Van Dong (Box 254)
  - The Phil Donahue Show (Box 254)
  - The Philadelphia Award (Box 254)
  - Philadelphia Psychoanalytic Society (Box 254)
  - Phillips Academy, Andover, MA (Box 254)
  - PHP Institute, Inc., Tokyo (Box 254)
  - Physicians Committee for Health Care for the Aged Through Social Security (Box 254)
  - Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine (PCRM) (Box 254)
  - Physicians for Automotive Safety (Box 255)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility (PSR), 1963-1985; 4 folders (Box 255)
  - The Physicians Forum, Inc. (Box 255)
  - Pickett, Clarence E. (Box 255)
  - Piedmont Rural Research Cooperative (Box 255)
  - Pierson, Emily M. (Box 255)
  - Pinochet, Augusto (Box 255)
  - Pips Parents House, Los Angeles, CA (Box 255)
  - Pittsburgh Pediatric Society (Box 255)
  - Pizzo, Peggy Daly (Box 255)
    See also Beacon Press.
  - The Plain Dealer, Cleveland, OH (Box 255)
  - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 2 folders (Box 255)
  - Planned Parenthood of Ontario (Box 256)
  - Planned Parenthood, World Population (Box 256)
  - Plassa, Corinne (Box 256)
  - Playboy (Box 256)
  - Playboy Press Paperbacks (Box 256)
  - Plowshares 8 Support Committee (Box 256)
  - Plymouth Institute, Plymouth Meeting, PA (Box 256)
  - Pochet, Jean Corneille (Box 256)
  - Pocket Books, 1946-1959; 4 folders (Box 256)
  - Pocket Books, 1960-1964; 7 folders (Box 257)
  - Pocket Books, 1965-1984; 5 folders (Box 258)
  - Pocket Books, 1985-2000; 6 folders (Box 259)
  - Pogrebin, Letty Cottin, 2 folders (Box 260)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (Box 260)
  - Polkinghorn, G. Richard (Box 260)
  - Pomeroy, Harlan and Barbara (Box 260)
  - Poor People's Campaign (Box 260)
  - Popular Mechanics (Box 260)
  - Por Los Niños / For The Children (Box 260)
  - Porter, Charles O. (Box 260)
  - Porterfield, John D. (Box 260)
  - Potomac Alliance, Washington, DC (Box 260)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr. (Box 260)
  - Practical Psychology for Physicians (Box 260)
  - Prentice Hall (Box 260)
  - Presbytery of Arkansas (Union) (Box 260)
  - President's Committee on Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Crime (Box 260)
  - President's Committee on Mental Retardation (Box 260)
  - President's Council on Youth Fitness (Box 260)
  - Pressley House, Large, PA (Box 260)
  - Price, Sherry (Box 260)
  - Princeton University (Box 260)
  - The Progressive (Box 260)
  - Progressive Labor Party (Box 261)
  - Project Air War (Box 261)
  - The Project for Victims of Family Violence (Box 261)
  - Project Relief, Inc. (Box 261)
  - Promoting Enduring Peace, Inc. (Box 261)
  - Proprioceptive Writing Center, Portland, ME (Box 261)
  - The Provisional Revolutionary Government of the Republic of South Vietnam, 2 folders (Box 261)
  - Proxmire, William (Box 261)
  - Prud'homme, Hector (Box 261)
  - Pryor, David, 2 folders (Box 261)
  - The Psychoanalytic Study of the Child (Box 261)
  - The PTA Magazine (Box 261)
  - Public Action Coalition on Toys (PACT) (Box 261)
  - Public Affairs Institute, Washington, DC (Box 261)
  - Public Affairs Pamphlets (Box 261)
  - Public Broadcasting Service (PBS) (Box 262)
  - Public Citizen, Inc. (Box 262)
  - Public Education Association (Box 262)
  - Public Forum on Nuclear Energy, Russelville, AR (Box 262)
  - Puerto Rican Youth Project for National Liberation (Box 262)
  - Pugwash Conferences (Box 262)
  - Quebec Campaign for Nuclear Disarmament (Box 262)
  - Queen's University, Kingston, Ontario, 2 folders (Box 262)
  - Rabinowitz, Peter MacGarr (Box 262)
  - The Radiation Workers Project (Box 262)
  - Radical Education Project (Box 262)
  - Radio Activities Iona College, New Rochelle, NY (Box 262)
  - Radioactivist Handbook (Box 262)
  - Radiotelevisão Portuguesa, E.P. (Box 262)
  - RAI Corporation (Box 262)
  - Rainbow Babies and Children's Hospital, Cleveland, OH (Box 262)
    See also Child rearing study.
  - Rainbow Visions (Box 262)
  - Ramah Hebrew School Winnipeg, Canada (Box 262)
  - Ramparts [magazine] (Box 262)
  - The Rand Corporation (Box 262)
  - Randall, Tony (Box 262)
  - Randolph, A. Philip (Box 262)
  - Random House (Box 262)
  - Rangel, Charles (Box 262)
  - Rankin, John (Box 262)
  - Rapoport, Roger (Box 262)
  - Raskin, Marcus G. (Box 262)
  - Rayburn, Sam (Box 263)
  - Raymond, Jill (Box 263)
  - Reach Out, Inc., Denver, CO (Box 263)
  - Reach: The Association for Children with Artificial Arms (Box 263)
  - The Reader's Digest (Box 263)
  - Reagan, Ronald (Box 263)
  - The Record, Hackensack, NJ (Box 263)
  - Redbook, 1961-1973; 6 folders (Box 263)
  - Redbook, 1973-1978; 6 folders (Box 264)
  - Redbook, 1979-1983; 6 folders (Box 265)
  - Redbook, 1984-1994; 9 folders (Box 266)
  - Redbook, undated (Box 267)
  - Redbook seminar, includes both the men's and women's; 3 folders (Box 267)
  - Redford, Robert (Box 267)
  - Redress (Box 267)
  - Rees, Thomas M. (Box 267)
  - Refregier, Anton (Box 267)
  - Refuse & Resist (Box 267)
  - Regional Addiction Prevention (RAP), Inc., Washington, DC (Box 267)
  - Reinhart, John (Box 267)
  - Religion and Labor Council of America (Box 267)
  - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights (Box 267)
  - Republican National Committee (Box 267)
  - Republicans for Peace (Box 267)
  - Republicans-Independents-Democrats United (Box 267)
  - Resist, 2 folders (Box 268)
  - The Resistance (Box 268)
  - The Responsible Society, London (Box 268)
  - Reston, James (Box 268)
  - Retinitis Pigmentosa Foundation (Box 268)
  - Reuther, Victor G. (Box 268)
  - Reuther, Walter P., See Citizens Crusade Against Poverty.
  - Review [magazine] (Box 268)
  - Rew, Cathy and David (Box 268)
  - Rhode Island Committee for Peace in Vietnam (Box 268)
  - Rhode Islanders for Safe Power (Box 268)
  - Rhodes, James A. (Box 268)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham (Box 268)
  - Richard Fulton, Inc. (Box 268)
  - Richter Productions, 2 folders (Box 268)
  - Rifkin, Jeremy (Box 268)
  - Rip Van Winkle Clinic, Hudson, NY (Box 268)
  - Ritey, Hector J. (Box 268)
  - Rittelmeyer, Louis F. (Box 268)
  - The River City Six (Box 268)
  - The Riverside Church, New York, NY (Box 268)
  - Robertson, A. Willis (Box 268)
  - Robinson, Tommy F. (Box 268)
  - Robson, Lane, 2 folders (Box 269)
  - Rochester (MN) Child Health Institute, 4 folders (Box 269)